[{"answer": "Too many stairs", "docId": "Panic_Room_Koepp.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Shoulda got an apartment", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Keep your voice down", "docId": "Panic_Room_Koepp.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "This was your department, my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "They're not supposed to be here", "docId": "Panic_Room_Koepp.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "They're not supposed to be here", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "That's why the key didn't work, they changed the locks", "docId": "Panic_Room_Koepp.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " Exactly how is fourteen days almost three weeks", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Fourteen day escrow, man, that's almost three weeks!  They shouldn't be here for another week!  They don't own this house yet", "docId": "Panic_Room_Koepp.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Fourteen business days.  Escrow is always business days", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "It's okay, my friend", "docId": "Panic_Room_Koepp.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "my friend is cool.  That's all you need to know", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": " Who is this guy", "docId": "Panic_Room_Koepp.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "This is insane.  I'm outta here", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "They won't get hurt", "docId": "Panic_Room_Koepp.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "my friend, what in God's name do we do if she has a gun", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Can't hear a thing", "docId": "Panic_Room_Koepp.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I don't know.  my friend us.  I don't know", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Wait", "docId": "Panic_Room_Koepp.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "They can't.  They can't get in here. No.  They can't", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " Fuck", "docId": "Panic_Room_Koepp.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Get the fuck out of my house", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Who else but God could think this shit up?  I spend ten years building those fucking rooms to keep people out, now I gotta figure out how to get in.  God, man, He just loves the irony", "docId": "Panic_Room_Koepp.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Can't.  Whole point.  Can't get in the room", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Uh uh", "docId": "Panic_Room_Koepp.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "He won't even know who it was", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Okay, okay!  Okay", "docId": "Panic_Room_Koepp.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Yeah.  Yeah, I got an idea.  I gotta check something", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "What do you want", "docId": "Panic_Room_Koepp.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "No, you can't come in", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " -- posed to mean", "docId": "Panic_Room_Koepp.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " Get the fuck away from me", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "The walls are steel, right", "docId": "Panic_Room_Koepp.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "NOT THAT ONE?", "qsentId": 34}]